Guide to the Friendship House Association records, 1904-1992 MS2142
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Funding Sources, 1940-1981; MS2142 Series 5; 14.5 Linear feet (Box 93, Box 94, Box 91, Box 92, Box 89, Box 90, Box 87, Box 88, Box 107, Box 111, Box 109, Box 108, Box 95, Box 110, Box 102, Box 103, Box 100, Box 101, Box 106, Box 104, Box 105, Box 84, Box 83, Box 86, Box 85, Box 98, Box 99, Box 96,
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: Material for 1978 campaign - (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: Agency directory, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: United Way Newsletter article on Friendship House -, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: United Way Newsletter article on Rosalyn Carter's visit, undated (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: Blue Cross Magazine article on Friendship House, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: Article on how funds were used, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: Budget request FY, 1980 - 12/1978 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: United Way - general, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: United Way Newsletter -, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: Budget request for 1982, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: Budget request for FY 1981, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - United Way and Predecessors, United Way: United Way Guidelines, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Local Private Funding: Junior League, 1940 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Local Private Funding: Junior League report, 1950 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Local Private Funding: Junior League of DC, 1957 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Local Private Funding: Junior League of DC, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - Local Private Funding: Junior League of DC, 1966 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - Local Private Funding: Junior League of DC volunteers, 1967 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - Local Private Funding: Junior League, 1969 (Box 111, Folder 25)
  - Local Private Funding: Request for grant, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 26)
  - Local Private Funding: Application for funds, 1977 (Box 111, Folder 27)
  - Local Private Funding: Junior League, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 28)
- Other Organizations, 1923-1981; MS2142 Series 6; 4.5 Linear feet (Box 112, Box 113, Box 114, Box 115, Box 116, Box 117, Box 118, Box 120, Box 119)
  This series contains newspapers, newsletters, programs, brochures, correspondence, and reports which document the Friendship House Association's involvement with local, regional, and national organizations. The materials in this series cover the dates 1923-81. The bulk of the collection materials are dated from 1960-75.
  Because so many Friendship House programs were child-oriented, the DC Schools were involved in formulating their programs, and likewise certain school programs and problems were discussed by Friendship House. Friendship House was involved in school policies and problems, especially of those in the neighborhood. Of particular interest in this series are records related to other Settlement Houses.
  - Other Organizations, undated (Box 112)
  - Washington Council of Churches:, 1960 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Washington Council of Churches:, 1961 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Washington Council of Churches:, 1962 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Washington Council of Churches:, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Washington Council of Churches:, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Washington Council of Churches:, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Social Action Council of Capitol East:, 1960 ca. (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Social Action Council of Capitol East:, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Social Action Council of Capitol East:, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Social Action Council of Capitol East:, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society: Tours of Houses, n.d, undated (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society:, 1961 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society:, 1962 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society:, 1963 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society:, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society:, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society:, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society:, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society:, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society:, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - "The Courier" 05/1954 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - "The Courier" 04/195. 23."Roll Call" 01/1963 (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Urban League Neighborhood Development Center Report, 1965 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - South East Civic Association, 1965-1966 (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - "The Uptown Citizen" 04/1966 (Box 112, Folder 26)
  - Urban League Neighborhood Development Center - report, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 27)
  - Directory of Neighborhood Organizations, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 28)
  - Community Services Directory, done by Friendship House, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 29)
  - Guide to Alternative Education - Capitol Hill Group Ministry, 1975 (Box 112, Folder 30)
  - Washington Urban League Survey, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 31)
  - Basic Neighborhood Profile - prediction for 1988, 1978 (Box 112, Folder 32)
  - "The Hill Rag" - issue on Market Day, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 33)
  - Other Organizations, undated (Box 113)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 1964 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 1965 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 1966 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 01/1967-03/1967 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 04/1967-06/1967 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 04/1967-09/1967 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 11/1967-12/1967 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 02/1968-03/1968 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 04/1968-06/1968 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 07/1968-09/1968 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 10/196812/1968 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 04/11/1969 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 04/25/1969 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 07/10/1969 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 07/24/1969 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator" 08/1969 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 09/11/1969 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 09/25/1969 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator" 10/1969 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator" 11/1969 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator" 03/1970 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - "Capitol Hill Spectator", 1971 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations, undated (Box 114)
  - Capitol Hill News, 1961 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Capitol Hill News, 1962 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Capitol Hill News, 1963 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill News, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill News, 1965 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Hill News, 1966 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Hill News 02/1967 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Hill News 03/1967 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Capitol Hill News 05/1967 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Capitol Hill News 06/1967 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Capitol Hill News 11/1972 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Capitol East Gazette, 1966 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Capitol East Gazette, 1967 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Capitol East Gazette, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Capitol East Gazette 01/1969 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Capitol East Gazette 06/1969 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Capitol East Gazette 07/1969 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Capitol East Gazette 10/1969 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Capitol East Gazette 11/1969 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Capitol East Gazette 01/1970 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Capitol East Gazette 02/1970 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Capitol East Community Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations, undated (Box 115)
  - The Southwester, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - The Southwester, 1978 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - The Southwester, 1979 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - DC Gazette Community Guide, 1970 ca. (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - DC Gazette Fall, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - DC Gazette 12/1971 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - DC Gazette 1972 Community Guide (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - DC Gazette 04/1972 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - DC Gazette 05/1972 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - DC Gazette 08/1972 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - DC Gazette 09/1972 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - DC Gazette 10/1972 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - DC Gazette 11/1972 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - DC Gazette 10/1973 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - DC Gazette, 1974-1975 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - DC Gazette 02/1975 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - DC Gazette 03/1975 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - DC Gazette 06/1975 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - DC Gazette 05/1976 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Other Organizations, undated (Box 116)
  - DC Schools: Letter to the Board of Education for Friendship House, 1930 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - DC Schools: Model Desegregation Plan, 1964 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - DC Schools: Report to Friendship House from Board of Education delegate to implement Columbia University study of DC Schools, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - DC Schools: Read-a-thon at Friendship House, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - DC Schools: The Edmonds School Case - accidental death at a nearby playground, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - DC Schools: Report "The Edmonds School Case" by Ayo Kobie, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - DC Schools: Training Project - Center for Educational Advancement, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - DC Schools: PACTS, school involvement, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - DC Schools: PACTS (Parents, Administrators, Community, Teachers, Students), 1974 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - DC Schools: Working Paper on Small Schools, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - DC Schools: Robert Parker Playground at Edmonds-Peabody School, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - DC Schools: PACTS, other schools information, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - DC Schools: Edmonds-Peabody Community School Integration Project-Lincoln-Bethune Children's Center, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - DC Schools: Edmonds-Peabody Curriculum Model, 1975-1976 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - DC Schools: "Special Report" newsletters, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - DC Schools: Board of Education meetings, 01/1977-06/1977 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - DC Schools: Board of Education meetings, 06/1977-12/1977 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - DC Schools: Board of Education meetings, 08/1978 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - DC Schools: Board of Education Annual Report, 1978 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - DC Schools: Feasibility Study for a Comprehensive High School, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Other Organizations, undated (Box 117)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1977 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1979 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education:, 1980 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - DC Citizens for Better Public Education: Retreat, 07/1980 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Other Organizations, undated (Box 118)
  - Settlement Houses: Social settlements in DC, 1936 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Settlement Houses: Christ Child, 1938-1939 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Settlement Houses: Barney House, 1939 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Settlement Houses: Plans for Southwest House, 1941 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Settlement Houses: Settlement Staff Workers Association, 1941 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Settlement Houses: Barney House, 1944 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Settlement Houses: Christopher House, Chicago, 1950 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Settlement Houses: Other settlements, general, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Settlement Houses: Self Study of Eight Settlement Houses, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Settlement Houses: Brochure "Washington's Settlements", 1955 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Settlement Houses: Southwest Neighborhood House, 1956 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Settlement Houses: Hull House, Chicago, 1957 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Settlement Houses: Jewish Social Services Agency, 1960 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Settlement Houses: Hollyday House, 1960 ca. (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Settlement Houses: Diamond Jubilee of Washington Settlements, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Settlement Houses: Southeast House, 1962-1963 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Settlement Houses: Christ Child, 1963-1966 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Settlement Houses: Barney House, 1963-1966 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Settlement Houses: Other settlements, general, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Settlement Houses: Fides House, 1964 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Settlement Houses: Northwest House, 1964-1966 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Settlement Houses: Hospitality House, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Settlement Houses: Southeast House, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - Settlement Houses: Southeast House, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Settlement Houses: Southeast House Development Program, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - Settlement Houses: Southeast House Newsletter, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - Settlement Houses: Hull House, Chicago -, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 27)
  - Settlement Houses: Black Social Workers Association - Retreat and Tour, 1974 (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - Settlement Houses: Hopkins House, Alexandria Virginia, 1975-1976 (Box 118, Folder 29)
  - Settlement Houses: Southwest Community House, 1978 (Box 118, Folder 30)
  - Settlement Houses: Brochures from various settlements n.d., undated (Box 118, Folder 31)
  - Settlement Houses: Brochures from various settlements n.d., undated (Box 118, Folder 32)
  - Other Organizations, undated (Box 119)
  - Social Work and Settlement Organizations: Washington Council of Social Agencies - Report, 1924-1925 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Social Work and Settlement Organizations: Washington Council of Social Agencies, 1925-1926 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Social Work and Settlement Organizations: Washington Council of Social Agencies, 1939-1942 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Social Work and Settlement Organizations: National Capital Area Federation of Settlements, 1950 ca. (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Social Work and Settlement Organizations: National Capital Area Federation of Settlements - draft, 1964 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1937 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1938-1939 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1939 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1940 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1940 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1943 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1943 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1950 ca. (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1956 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1957 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Washington Federation of Settlements:, 1958 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - National Association of Social Workers:, 1957 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - National Association of Social Workers: (Newsletters), 1965 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - National Association of Social Workers:, 1966 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - National Association of Social Workers:, 1967 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - National Association of Social Workers: (Newsletters), 1969 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - National Association of Social Workers:, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - National Association of Social Workers: National Federation of Settlements, 1923 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - National Association of Social Workers: Definition of a settlement, 1937 (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - National Association of Social Workers: National Federation of Settlements, 1938-1939 (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - National Association of Social Workers: Settlement Staff Workers Association of DC -, 1940 (Box 119, Folder 26)
  - National Federation of Settlements:, 1923 (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Personnel Practices Code, 1947 (Box 119, Folder 28)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Newsletter, 1949 (Box 119, Folder 29)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Standards Statement, 1950 (Box 119, Folder 30)
  - National Federation of Settlements: DC Chapter, 1951 (Box 119, Folder 31)
  - National Federation of Settlements: DC Chapter, 1952 (Box 119, Folder 32)
  - National Federation of Settlements: DC Chapter, 1953 (Box 119, Folder 33)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Standards, 1954 (Box 119, Folder 34)
  - National Federation of Settlements: DC Chapter, 1954 (Box 119, Folder 35)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Bylaws, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 36)
  - National Federation of Settlements: general, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 37)
  - National Federation of Settlements: general, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 38)
  - National Federation of Settlements and Neighborhood Centers Newsletters (same organization, name change), 11/1955-12/1955 (Box 119, Folder 39)
  - Other Organizations, undated (Box 120)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Statement on civil rights, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Newsletters, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Brochure, 1957-1958 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Summary of workshop, 1958 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Correspondence, 1958 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Financial statement, 1958 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Correspondence, 1959 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Meeting at Friendship House of the group, 1959 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Statement of human rights, 1959 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Brochure, 1960 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - National Federation of Settlements: DC chapter - Luncheon Program of DC Settlements, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Report, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Report, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - National Federation of Settlements: National Federation Code, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Social Policy Platform, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Correspondence, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Directory, 1963-1964 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Correspondence, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Correspondence, minutes, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Directory, 1964-1965 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Brochures, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Financial statements, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Salary standards, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Directory, 1965-1966 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Brochures, 1965-1966 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Statement on Program cuts, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Bylaws, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Directory, 1966-1967 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Correspondence, brochures, 1972 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Annual Report, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Meeting, 1975 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Newsletter, 09/1977-10/1977 (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - National Federation of Settlements: Careers Brochure - n.d., undated (Box 120, Folder 35)
- Oversized Records, 1940-1967; MS2142 Series 7; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 121)
  This series contains photographs as well as other materials that required oversize storage. The materials in this series covers the dates 1940-67.
  - Oversized Records, undated (Box 121)
  - USO Activities - photos of Servicemen and young women at a piano, 1940 ca. (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Boys basketball - two-part large photographs, 1940 ca. (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Women's Group photo, 1942 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Children's Art Classes - children at easels, 1940 ca. (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Children's Art Classes - integrated group of children doing art work with poster paints, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Children's Art Classes with Hans Klagsbrunn, director, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    (integrated group of children doing art work
  - Children s' Art Classes, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Duplicate photos (photos noted elsewhere in the collection), undated (Box 121, Folder 8)
    Lady Bird Johnson with neighborhood children and Secret Service Agents at Friendship House 1967, Children visit the Capitol with Congressional Secretaries' Club 1966, Children visit a museum, on the steps, Children painting 1959, Children painting 1940.